SHIVSHANKAR SHEJWAL

FRONT-END SOFT ENGINEER QUALYS INFOSEC. (SHIVAJINAGAR)

JOINING DATE: 21-JAN-

2019

EFFECTIVE EXP: 2YR 3

MONTH

CONTACT

+91 774 738 4723 SHEJWAL1SHIVSHANKAR@GMAIL.C OM

SOCIAL MEDIA

LINKEDIN: @SHIVSHANKAR-SHEJWAL-829BA296/

PROFILE

I am 2.5 years experienced UI developer currently working in Qualys Infosec Pune.I have keen intrest and passion toward UI and I am really enthusiatic for working in React.js,Node.js, cutting edge UI technologies, related frameworks and libraries.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SAQ VRM AND CSM (QUALYS) FEB 2019 - PRESENT

• Worked on vendor on-boarding screens and delivered UI well before time.

AIRWIRE (27 OCT 2018 - 10 JAN 2019) FREELANCING

• Worked on fixing some important bugs, created user bounty ui flow in vue.js

AUTODESK COMMUNITY PROJECT(LEGACY AND BR)

DEC 2016 - FEB 2017 AND JULY 2017- 10 JAN2019 (PERSISTENT) HTTPS://FORUMS.AUTODESK.COM

- Learned Lithium platform, socializing, google analytics lithium practices.
- Worked on integrations with Beehive, Oxygen, Google Tag Manager, AKN platform.

BADGEVILLE CONNECTOR PROJECT

FEB 2017- JUNE2017 (PERSISTENT)

- Successfully determined which API to use between Cairo and legacy API's.
- Using event subscription framework developed connector and embedded Badgeville js API's which would show gamification UI upon events like message create or like given.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING

GOVT COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING AURANGABAD | 2012 - 2016

GPA: 7.422

SKILLS

- Javascript
- React.is
- HTML ,CSS3 and Preprocessor
- Redux

- Webpack
- Learning Node.js
- Know Vue.js
- Git

CERTIFICATIONS

- Advanced javascript Udemy https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-ZH9Q61SN/
- Complete css guide with Sass, flexbox, grid Udemy https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-ZH9Q61SN/